{
    "id": "8cd3ad4716294ffeb92f13c5a33c671f",
    "title": "Preposition after adjectives",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "64e942aaf54445e78221dd038265bf7b",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Theresa has been married …………….. Charles for thirty years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Alex is married ……………….. three kids.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your hair color is similar ……………….. mine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "than"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is interested ……………….. philosophy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "in",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are responsible ………………. the mess.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "with",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "That is typical ………………… her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "off",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am sick ……………….. his erratic behavior.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "of",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is quite capable ………………. defending himself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "As I was short ……………… cash, I borrowed some from my uncle.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "of",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wasn’t aware …………………. his motives.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "for",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susie is quite good …………………. solving puzzles.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}